# SEYED MOHAMMAD

## SHEIKH AHMADI

## **CONTACT INFO**

**E-mail** smsag99@gmail.com , info@sheikh-ahmadi.ir

**Phone** +98 9184163875

Address Sanandaj, Kurdistan, Iran

Website sheikh-ahmadi.ir

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a Computer Engineer Student at the **University of Kurdistan** and also extremely passionate about programming and research. I have founded a firm named **VGostar** in the Augmented Reality (AR) field at the University of Kurdistan, and also we have been funded by university.

Recently, I have been working in an accelerator firm named **Zharfa** as a back-end developer using Node.js. We are working on some commercial projects.

In 2021, I participated in a research project managed by **Dr. Sina Ahmadi** from the George Mason University and **Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar** from the University of Kurdistan. It is supposed to be submitted soon.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## CO-FOUNDER AND BACK-END DEVELOPER

2022-Present

**VGostar** | Sanandaj, Iran

• Implementation of AR technology

#### JUNIOR BACK-END DEVELOPER

2022-Present

**Zharfa Accelerator Academy** | Sanandaj, Iran

• Commercial projects.

## **EDUCATION**

## **BA IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING**

2018-2022

**University of Kurdistan** | Sanandaj, Iran

- Accepting and being funded a firm related to AR technology by the university
- Research assistant (RA) and teaching assistant (TA)
- Student Union

## **VOLUNTEER**

#### RA

- Research assistant in **EndoLink** Project with **Dr. Sina Ahmadi** at George Mason University and Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar at University of kurdistan.
- Research assistant in **KurdNet** Project with **Dr. Sina Ahmadi** at George Mason University and Dr. Fatemeh Daneshfar at University of kurdistan.

## TA

• Teaching assistant of "Fundamentals of Computer Programming" course with C programming language, with Dr. Amanj Khorramian at University of kurdistan.

## STUDENT UNION

Member of IOT student union

## WORKSHOPS

#### **CEH SECURITY WORKSHOP**

• CEH Security Course presented by Moslem Haghighian.

#### **IOT WORKSHOP**

• IOT Workshop with Arduino.

#### KOTLIN PROGRAMMING WORKSHOP

• Building an android application with kotlin.

## **SKILLS**

● ● ● Node.js, JavaScript, C#
-------------------------------

$$ullet$$
  $ullet$   $ullet$  O Asp.net, Unity, Java, Arduino, C

Jekyll, Python, Kotlin

## Languages

- English (Full professional proficiency)
- Persian (Native)
- Kurdish (Native)

## REFERENCES

Postdoctoral Researcher Dr. Sina George Mason University Ahamdi sahmad46@gmu.edu

**Assistant Professor** Dr. Amanj Khorramian University of Kurdistan a.khorramian@uok.ac.ir

Dr. Fatemeh **Daneshfar** 

Dean of Department of Computer Engineering University of Kurdistan f.daneshfar@uok.ac.ir